HAFIZ ELFIA WEDO PUTRA



Contact

Address:

KOMP. PCI BLOK E 27 A NO. 02 Cilegon, Banten 42423

Place /date of Birth:

Cilegon, June 22, 2000

Phone:

+62 87724006119

Status:

Single

Email:

hafizelfiawedoputra@outlook.com

Website:

hafizewp22.github.io

Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/hafizewp/

Languages

Bahasa Indonesia English Fluent Elementary

Hard Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- PHP
- Java
- Laravel
- Android Studio (Java)
- MySQL / SQL
- Database Design
- Figma (Software)
- Data Analysis

Summary

I have experience in web development at my internship company and I am interested in technology. I am also a hard worker, have integrity, responsibility and work in a team. Really likes to learn coding such as UI/UX, websites and data analysis to create interesting programs.

Experience

Web Developer - PT. Telkom Indonesia

Internship

March 2022 – Present

- This section serves as a Web Developer to help companies check and update/create websites using Laravel and ReactJS.

Student Mentor - Bina Nusantara University

Friends Care Community - Peer Partner

October 2021 – Present

 The Community Care for Friends at BINUS University which provides the task of helping friends who have special attention and high concern for disability issues and special needs on campus.

Organization – Bina Nusantara Computer Club (BNCC)

Learning and Training (LnT) Staff

August 2020 – Present

- Establish curriculum and class materials and schedules for classes and teaching.
- Become an event committee in organizations related to Information Technology.
- Create and do attendance for each LnT class.

Training - Digital Talent Scholarship

Training - Database Design and Programming with SQL

July 2021 – October 2021

 Scholarship program from the Ministry of Communication and Information of the Republic of Indonesia and supported by Oracle Academy with the theme Database Design and Programming with SQL.

Organization – Bina Nusantara Computer Club (BNCC)

Activist

September 2019 – August 2020

- Student Leadership and Management Exercises (LKMM).
- Training and Learning to create Website design (HTML & CSS).

Education

Bachelor's Degree: Computer Science, 2019 - Present

Bina Nusantara University, Jakarta, ID

Streaming: Database Technology, GPA: 3,23 / 4,0

Vocational School: **Software Engineering**, 2016 - 2019 **Vocational High School of Informatics**, Serang, ID

Score: 81 / 100

Soft Skills

- Leadership
- Teamwork
- Time Management

Honors & Awards

- **2021** Designing UI/UX with Figma Competition Bina Nusantara University 3rd Winner - Campus level
- **2020** Asia Jakarta Indonesia National Contest (INC) 2020 International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) 70th ranking of 700 teams - National level
- 2018 Sister School 3 Student Exchange To Thailand
 Student exchange to one of the best schools in Bangkok,
 Thailand, namely Matthayom Watnairong School and
 exchange of culture, language and new knowledge and
 cooperation between the two schools.

Certificates

- Introduction to HTML5 (University of Michigan)
- Introduction to Data Studio (Google)
- HTML Course (Sololearn)
- Learn to Code with Python by Udemy
- Database Design by Oracle Academy
- Database Programming with SQL by Oracle Academy
- SQL (Basic) by HackerRank
- Frontend Weekly Workshop
- Web Development Path (Node.js) by Progate
- Database Coaching by Course-Net Indonesia, B+
- Java (Basic) by HackerRank
- Problem Solving (Basic) by HackerRank
- IC3 GS5 Key Applications (Office 2016), 906 / 1000

Research

 Augmented Reality For Human Digestive Anatomy Biology Learning

www.scribd.com/document/521632106/Augmented-Reality-for-Human-Digestive-Anatomy-Biology-Learning

Augmented Reality Technology research for 5 months, through Augmented Reality applications that have been made and then tested on teachers and students in high school, and the results of the research are successful.

June 2021